

Apostolos Gouvalas Full-stack Web Developer

Full-stack developer with over 7 years of experience in PHP, SQL, and JavaScript, among other languages. With attention to detail and a passion for problem-solving, I am eager to contribute my skills to dynamic and challenging projects.

□ apo.gouv@gmail.com

**\( +30-6978811469** 

cubedesigns.gr

• Thessaloniki, Greece

### SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/apostolos-gouvalas

github.com/ApoGouv

#### **EDUCATION**

MS in Mobile and Web Computing

2016 - 2018

[ Distinction ]

International Hellenic University (Thessaloniki, Greece)

Digital Systems Degree, majoring in "Communication and Network Systems"

2004 - 2013

University of Piraeus - Department of Digital Systems (Piraeus, Athens, Greece)

## **LANGUAGES**

Greek [Native language]
English [Proficiency of Michigan & IELTS 7.5]
Spanish [A2 in progress]

#### **SOFTWARE & TOOLS**

VSCode, Git, Linux, Windows, cPanel, etc.

## **HOBBIES**

Cycling, Dancing Salsa/ Kizomba, Sudoku, Rock Music

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Web Developer

Nov 2017 - Present | Mental Media (former MultiHosting)

- Developed e-commerce websites using platforms such as OpenCart, CS-Cart, PrestaShop, WooCommerce, etc., integrating custom functionalities and ERP programs.
- Website development including portfolios, corporate sites, personal websites, etc., using platforms such as WordPress, Joomla, etc.
- Contributed to various company projects utilizing technologies such as WHMCS, Laravel, vBulletin, Joomla, etc.

# Front-end Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 | PSDGator

 Converted design mockups from PSD or Al files to valid HTML and CSS, or WordPress themes.

## Full-stack Web Developer

Dec 2015 - Present | Freelance

 Develop websites, e-shops, and custom solutions according to customer requirements.

## Front-end Web Developer

Apr 2014 - May 2014 | igraphics.gr

 Created the user interface, based on supplied graphic mockups, for applications to visualize the results of the 2014 Italian European Parliament Elections and display past Italian election results, using valid HTML, CSS, and jQuery.

## **CERTIFICATES**

JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP, etc.

2017 - 2024 | Udemy

Build a Social Network from Scratch: JavaScript PHP + MySQL Jan 01, 2019

The Complete Node.js Developer Course (2nd Edition)

Course (2nd Edition) Oct 09, 2017

The Complete JavaScript Course:

Build a Real-World Project Sep 11, 2017

JavaScript Essentials Aug 14, 2017